<Example>
    <Name>
        NVIC_IRQPriority_Example
    </Name>
    <Description>
        This example demonstrates the use of the Nested Vectored Interrupt Controller (NVIC): 
		- Configuration of 2 EXTI Lines (SEL button EXTI Line & KEY button EXTI Line)
  to generate an interrupt on each falling edge and use the SysTick interrupt.
- These interrupts are configured with the following parameters:
    - SEL button EXTI Line:  
        - PreemptionPriority = PreemptionPriorityValue
        - SubPriority = 0
    - KEY button EXTI Line:    
        - PreemptionPriority = 0
        - SubPriority = 1           
    - SysTick Handler:  
        - PreemptionPriority = !PreemptionPriorityValue
        - SubPriority = 0             
First, the PreemptionPriorityValue is equal to 0, the SEL button EXTI Line 
has higher preemption priority than the SysTick handler. 

In the KEY button EXTI Line interrupt routine the SEL button EXTI Line and 
SysTick preemption priorities are inverted. 
In the SEL button EXTI Line interrupt routine the pending bit of the SysTick 
interrupt is set this will cause SysTick ISR to preempt the SEL button EXTI 
Line ISR only if it has higher preemption priority.
The system behaves as following:
 
1) The first time KEY button EXTI Line interrupt occurs the SysTick preemption 
become higher than SEL button EXTI Line one. So when the SEL button EXTI 
Line interrupt occurs, the SysTick ISR is executed and the PreemptionOccured 
variable become TRUE and the four leds (LED1, LED2, LED3, LED4) start toggling.

2) When the next KEY button EXTI Line interrupt occurs the SysTick preemption
become lower than SEL button EXTI Line one. So when the SEL button EXTI Line
interrupt occurs and it will be not preempted by Systick ISR, the PreemptionOccured 
variable became FALSE and the four leds (LED1, LED2, LED3, LED4) stop toggling.

Then this behavior is repeated from point 1) in an infinite loop.
    </Description>
    <Version>
        1.0.0
    </Version>
    <Tags>
        NVIC_IRQPriority
    </Tags>
    <EVKit>
        STM32303C-EVAL Evaluation Board
    </EVKit>
    <Files>
        <File>
            $REPO_ROOT$\ST\STM32F30X\cmsis_lib\NVIC\example\NVIC_IRQPriority\src\NVIC_IRQPriority_Example.c
        </File>
    </Files>
    <Dependencys>
        <Dependency>RCC,GPIO,EXTI</Dependency>
    </Dependencys>
</Example>


