<Example>
    <Name>
        USART_DaExInt_Example
    </Name>
    <Description>
      This example provides a small application in which joystick buttons are used 
to trigger USART communication using interrupts and though using USART firmware 
library.

- Hardware Description

To use this example, you need to load it on two STM32F30x boards (let's call them 
Board A and Board B) then connect these two boards through UART lines and GND.
On Board A, at each joystick buttons press:
- The USART Board A sends the specific command to the USART Board B (the command 
  contains the transaction code (CMD_RIGHT, CMD_LEFT, CMD_UP, CMD_DOWN or CMD_SEL)
  followed by the number of data to be transmitted (CMD_RIGHT_SIZE, CMD_LEFT_SIZE, 
  CMD_UP_SIZE, CMD_DOWN_SIZE or CMD_SEL_SIZE)

- The USART Board B receives the command and sends the CMD_ACK command to the USART board A

- The USART Board A receives the CMD_ACK command and sends the number of bytes 
  from TxBuffer to the USART Board B.

- The USART Board B compares the number of bytes received with the defined ones into
  his TxBuffer.
  
  Received data correctness is signaled by LED lightening and though as follow:
   - Joystick RIGHT and data correctly received ==> LD2, LD3 ON and LD4 OFF 
   - Joystick LEFT and data correctly received  ==> LD4 ON, LD2 and LD3 are OFF
   - Joystick UP and data correctly received    ==> LD2 ON, LD3 and LD4 are OFF
   - Joystick DOWN and data correctly received  ==> LD3 ON, LD2 and LD4 are OFF
   - Joystick SEL and data correctly received   ==> LD2, LD3 and LD4 are ON

The steps described above can be also initiated and ensured by Board B. 

In both boards(Board A or Board B), the data transfers is managed using USART1_IRQHandler 
in stm32f30x_it.c file when USART1 is used.

The SysTick is configured to generate interrupt each 10ms. A dedicated counter 
inside the SysTick ISR is used to toggle the LD1 each 100ms indicating that the 
firmware is running.
A defined communication timeout is insuring that the application will not remain 
stuck if the USART communication is corrupted.
You can adjust this timeout through the USER_TIMEOUT  define inside main.h file
depending on CPU frequency and application conditions (interrupts routines, 
number of data to transfer, baudrate, CPU frequency...).

These operations can be repeated infinitely.
    </Description>
    <Version>
        1.0.0
    </Version>
    <Tags>
        USART_DaExInt
    </Tags>
    <EVKit>
        STM32303C-EVAL Evaluation Board
    </EVKit>
    <Files>
        <File>
            $REPO_ROOT$\ST\STM32F30X\cmsis_lib\USART\example\USART_DataExchangeInterrupt\src\USART_DaExInt_Example.c
        </File>
    </Files>
    <Dependencys>
        <Dependency>RCC,GPIO,NVIC</Dependency>
    </Dependencys>
</Example>


