<Example>
    <Name>
        CRC_TwoBoards
    </Name>
    <Description>
  This example aims to show how to verify CRC checksum while USART communication
between two STM32F30x boards.

- Hardware Description

To use this example, you need to load it on two STM32F30x boards (let's call them 
Board A and Board B) then connect these two boards through UART lines and GND.

In the firmware example uncomment the dedicated line in the main.h file to use
the USART peripheral as TRANSMITTER device or as RECIVER device.

- The connection between the pins should use a common Ground.

@verbatim
*------------------------------------------------------------------------------*
|                BOARD A                                BOARD B                |
|         ____________________                   ____________________          |
|        |                    |                 |                    |         |
|        |     TRANSMITTER    |                 |      RECIVER       |         | 
|        |     __________     |                 |     __________     |         |
|        |    |   USART  |____|TX_____________RX|____|   USART  |    |         |
|        |    |  Device1 |____|RX_____________TX|____|  Device2 |    |         |
|        |    |__________|    |                 |    |__________|    |         |
|        |                    |                 |                    |         |
|        |  O LD1             |                 |  O LD1             |         |
|        |  O LD2    Joystick |                 |  O LD2    Joystick |         |
|        |  O LD3        _    |                 |  O LD3        _    |         |
|        |              |_|   |                 |              |_|   |         |
|        |                    |                 |                    |         |
|        |             GND O--|-----------------|--O GND             |         |
|        |____________________|                 |____________________|         |
|                                                                              |
|                                                                              |
*------------------------------------------------------------------------------*
@endverbatim

- Software Description

The CRC peripheral is configured to use the 8-bit CRC polynomial x8 + x7 + x6 + x4 + x2 + 1 
with the initialization value is set to 0.

On Board A, at each joystick SEL button press:

- The USART Board A sends data already defined in TxBuffer.

- CRC value is computed during USART data transfer.  

- After computing CRC of latest transferred byte, TxBuffer is updated with final CRC value.

- The USART Board A sends latest byte which is the final computed CRC value.

On Board B,

- The USART Board B receives the data (data + CRC value) in RxBuffer.

- CRC value of received data are computed in Board B and compared with the received one.
  
  CRC checksum result is signaled by LED lightening as following:
    - CRC received and computed values are equal ==> LD2 toggles, LED4 OFF. 
    - CRC received and computed values are not equal ==> LD2 Off, LED4 ON. 

The SysTick is configured to generate interrupt each 10ms. A dedicated counter 
inside the SysTick ISR is used to toggle the LD1 each 100ms indicating that the 
firmware is running.
    </Description>
    <Version>
        1.0.0
    </Version>
    <Tags>
        CRC_TwoBoards
    </Tags>
    <EVKit>
        STM32303C-EVAL Evaluation Board
    </EVKit>
    <Files>
        <File>
            $REPO_ROOT$\ST\STM32F30X\cmsis_lib\CRC\example\CRC_TwoBoards\src\CRC_TwoBoards.c
        </File>
    </Files>
    <Dependencys>
        <Dependency>RCC,NVIC,GPIO,USART,EXTI</Dependency>
    </Dependencys>
</Example>


