<Example>
    <Name>
        RTC_Calendar_Example
    </Name>
    <Description>
     
This example demonstrates and explains how to setup the RTC peripheral, in 
terms of prescaler and interrupts, to be used to keep time and to generate 
alarm interrupt. 

One from the following clock can be used as RTC clock source (uncomment the
corresponding define in main.c): 
  - LSE oscillator clock usually delivered by a 32.768 kHz quartz.
  - LSI oscillator clock

A key value is written in backup data register 0 to indicate if the RTC is already
configured.

The program behaves as follows:

1. After startup the user is asked to set the time and alarm (entered on HyperTerminal).

2. When an External Reset occurs the BKP domain is not reset and the RTC configuration
   is not lost.

3. When power on reset occurs:
    - the BKP domain is reset and the RTC configuration is lost (JP16 must be in pos 1-2).

4. When an RTC Alarm A event occurs the RTC Alarm interrupt is generated and the
   LED1 is on.
   
The example uses HyperTerminal to configure the RTC clock and display the current time:
 - When SEL button is pressed, a menu is displayed to configure the RTC Time and 
   Alarm A registers.
 - When Key button is pressed, the current time is displayed.
 - When UP button is pressed, the current alarm A is displayed. 

LED2 is turned ON when the RTC configuration is done correctly.
 
The EVAL_COM1 is configured as follow:
    - BaudRate = 115200 baud  
    - Word Length = 8 Bits (7 data bit + 1 parity bit)
    - One Stop Bit
    - No parity
    - Hardware flow control disabled (RTS and CTS signals)
    - Receive and transmit enabled
    </Description>
    <Version>
        1.0.0
    </Version>
    <Tags>
        RTC_Calendar
    </Tags>
    <EVKit>
        STM32303C-EVAL Evaluation Board
    </EVKit>
    <Files>
        <File>
            $REPO_ROOT$\ST\STM32F30X\cmsis_lib\RTC\example\RTC_Calendar\src\RTC_Calendar_Example.c
        </File>
    </Files>
    <Dependencys>
        <Dependency>GPIO,RCC,NVIC,PWR,EXTI,USART,C library</Dependency>
    </Dependencys>
</Example>


