<Example>
    <Name>
        CAN_DualFIFO
    </Name>
    <Description>
  This example shows how to configure the CAN peripheral to send and receive 
CAN frames in normal mode and using FIFO0 and FIFO1. The sent frames are used to control Leds 
by pressing key or SEL push buttons.
For the sent frames two different.standard identifier are used "0x321" is used when 
pressing SEL and the other one (0x123) is transmited by pressing on KEY push button .

The CAN serial communication link is a bus to which a number of units may be
connected. This number has no theoretical limit. Practically the total number
of units will be limited by delay times and/or electrical loads on the bus line.


This program behaves as follows:
  - By Pressing on SEL Button : LED1 turns ON and all other Leds are OFF, on the N
    eval boards connected to the bus. 
  - Press on SEL Button again to send CAN Frame to command LEDn+1 ON, all other Leds 
    are OFF on the N eval boards.

  - By Pressing on KEY Button : LED4 turns ON and all other Leds are OFF, on the N
    eval boards connected to the bus. 
  - Press on KEY Button again to send CAN Frame to command LEDn-1 ON, all other Leds 
    are OFF on the N eval boards.
    
  - The USER can use KEY and SEL in the same time to Control LEDs.
@note This example is tested with a bus of 3 units. The same program example is 
      loaded in all units to send and receive frames.
@note Any unit in the CAN bus may play the role of sender (by pressing KEY/SEL button)
      or receiver.

The CAN is configured as follow:
    - Bit Rate   = 1 Mbit/s  
    - CAN Clock  = external clock (HSE)
    - ID Filter for FIFO0: 0x123 identifiers are allowed
    - ID Filter for FIFO1: 0x321 identifiers are allowed 
    - RTR = Data
    - DLC = 1 byte
    - Data: Led number that should be turned ON

- STM32303C-EVAL Set-up
    - Use LED1, LED2, LED3 and LED4 connected respectively to PE.08, PE.09, PE.10
      and PE.11 pins
    - Use KEY Push Button connected to PE.06 
    - Use SEL Push Button connected to PC.13 
    - Connect a female/female CAN cable between at least 2 EVAL CAN connectors (CN3)
    - Jumper JP3 must be fitted.
    - Jumper JP4 must be fitted in 1-2 position.
    </Description>
    <Version>
        1.0.0
    </Version>
    <Tags>
        CAN_DualFIFO
    </Tags>
    <EVKit>
        STM32303C-EVAL Evaluation Board
    </EVKit>
    <Files>
        <File>
            $REPO_ROOT$\ST\STM32F30X\cmsis_lib\CAN\example\CAN_DualFIFO\src\CAN_DualFIFO.c
        </File>
    </Files>
    <Dependencys>
        <Dependency>RCC,NVIC,GPIO,SPI,EXTI</Dependency>
    </Dependencys>
</Example>


